Guide to the Wesley C. Salmon Papers, 1950-2003 ASP.2003.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Library Materials, 1970-2001; VII.
  - Thesis and Dissertation written by Salmon, 1950s; 2.
    Salmon's Ph.D. dissertation and M.A. thesis are found here.
    - Whitehead's Conception of Freedom. University of Chicago, 1947 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - John Venn's Theory of Induction. University of California, Los Angeles., 1950 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Translations of Salmon's Work, 1950-2001; 3.
    - Salmon, Wesley. 40 Anni di Apiegazione Scientifica. Padova: Franco Muzzio, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Salmon, Wesley. Logica. Mexico: Derechos Reservados, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Salmon, Wesley. Logica: Segunda Edicao. Rio De Janeiro: Zahar, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Salmon, Wesley. Logica: Quarta Edicao. Rio De Janeiro: Zahar, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Salmon, Wesley. Logica Elementare. Bologna: Il Mulino, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Salmon, Wesley. Logik. Stuttgart: Reclam, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 8)